Whoa! That's awesome!
Krai, are all these relics yours?
It's impressive how many you've collected.
Yup.
I've got a thing for relics,
so I just buy them whenever I can.
Hey, Krai!
You'll pick out one of these
relics just for me, right?
Yeah. I did promise, after all.
No fair, Liz.
He's going to pick one for all of us, too!
It's finally paying off that
our leader is a hoarder.
It's about time I get my just rewards
for being asked to charge them all the time.
And I really am grateful.
Krai.
What's this relic?
Oh, that?
It's a Magic Bag.
It can hold a lot more than it looks.
So, it can warp space?
It's difficult to do that with magic.
Wasn't it expensive?
Nope, it was super cheap.
It can only store chocolate.
Huh?
Only chocolate...
So, it's completely useless.
Krai! This bracelet is so cute!
That's a...
Are you all right?
That's a Labyrinth Ring.
Putting it on completely messes up
all your spatial senses.
This is terrible.
Usually, the confusion would cause
your reflexes to tear your body apart.
You're really something, Liz.
This sword is the coolest!
Wait, that's...
a cursed sword.
I want to cut people to shreds!
To shreds!
Again?!
Liz!
Indeed.
Let me cut!
Let me cut people!
Yes, that sword usually makes people
completely lose their minds,
but it's crazy that he's
not that different...
Let me cut people!
You're really something, Luke.
Let me cut them!
Yes, yes!
Yup.
I want to cut them up!
Afterward,
these dangerous relics were fortunately
turned into training gear for Luke and Liz.
Perfect!
What's that?
This is a purchase order.
For what?
"The Mysterious Mask Wants to Fight."
Episode 04
The Mysterious Mask Wants to Fight
Let This Grieving Soul Retire
The White Wolf's Den is a maze made up of
narrow passageways that keep branching.
I just found out about this,
but in short...
No matter how much you walk,
everything looks the same,
so you never know where you are.
And why the hell am I taking point, anyway?
Tino and Rhuda are the thieves.
Why doesn't one of them take point?
She won't even look at me.
Does Tino hate me?
I don't even want to talk to you.
Please die.
Is that what's she's thinking?
Even though she liked me so much before?
Maybe I should've gotten on my
knees and apologized first.
So...
My apologies if this is
all according to plan,
but where exactly are we headed?
Toward the exit?
Where else but the exit?
Not sure if this is the right way, but...
Gilbert.
Yeah?
Figuring out Master's plan
is part of the training.
Also, we've been moving away
from the exit this whole time.
What?!
Since I checked a map before setting out,
I have a rough idea of
the layout of this den.
No matter what we do, this path
will never get us to the exit.
If we want to return, we've got
to go back to the boss chamber.
I didn't know.
I didn't know!
Wait, so were those big wolf
things earlier the bosses?
That explains why they looked so strong.
Hey, Krai.
I understand that this is
all part of our training,
but could you at least tell
us where we're headed...
I'd love to know that myself.
Why the hell is everyone
relying on me, anyway?
Guess it's time we made a turn.
That's impossible!
How?
I told you.
Everything Master does, he does for a reason.
Come on, hurry up!
Y-Yeah.
Is that...
Hang in there.
Are you all right?
You guys actually saw them?
Hunters have such good eyesight.
Wait a minute.
Is that the party we're supposed to rescue?
I am Rudolph Davout, the party leader.
Thank you for coming to rescue us.
You can express your gratitude to Master.
Huh?
He's the one who figured
everything out and led us here.
Not really.
This was all just a coincidence.
Master!
Why would he say that himself?
That makes him even more inscrutable.
I gave them some potions,
but their energy is completely depleted.
They need to eat something.
Oh, yeah!
I've got that thing.
What thing?
I knew it.
Master is a god.
There's plenty more,
so eat as many as you like.
How does that work?
That's a secret.
Master really is amazing.
Not only did he save our worthless hides,
he also found the lost party with such ease.
But what's more impressive
is his ability to calm everyone
in this tense situation with his antics.
Tino.
Go on. Eat.
I knew it!
He's a god!
I'm glad everyone is alive.
When I'd heard that everyone in
the missing party was level 5,
I was sure it must have
been some kind of mistake!
We weren't prepared, either.
We never expected the
enemy to be that strong.
Wait a second.
Those wolf knights were pretty strong,
but I wouldn't have expected them to
completely dominate a level 5 party.
Wolves?
Yeah.
With their faces half-covered by bone.
No. Not them.
The thing that got us was a single enemy...
A small phantom with its
entire face covered by a skull.
That thing is hatred incarnate.
That phantom is probably the manifestation
of the lingering curse of the Silver Moon.
After the humans exterminated
the wolf monsters,
their hatred swelled inside the treasure
vault and turned into this incredible power.
Otherwise, that amount of power...
simply can't be explained.
We are confident in our abilities,
but we stood absolutely no chance.
You bastard!
It was on another level.
It was so strong...
it might even be on the
level of Thousand Swords.
Did you just say Thousand Swords?!
You mean the capital's
strongest swordsman?!
Thousand Swords, huh?
As the Sword Saint's apprentice, he got
his education in proper swordsmanship.
Using that as the foundation, he went on to
learn all manner of sword fighting styles.
He's a complete sword nerd who can cut down
any enemy with a single wooden sword.
There's no need to hide it: he's my
childhood friend and a member of the Grievers,
Luke Sykol.
"Thousand Swords"
Luke Sykol
Hunter Level 6
I want to cut people!
I'm sure this "hatred
incarnate" is really strong,
but saying it's on the level of
Thousand Swords is a bit much.
If such a phantom existed, Luke would
have come and cut it down ages ago.
But yeah...
I don't think Tino can beat it.
I knew I should've just waited for Ark!
Back then, the way it refused to finish us
off, you'd think it was toying with us...
Next time, it will kill us for sure.
What are you going to do, Krai?
Um, why are you asking me?
Then it sounds like our only choice is to
get out of here before we encounter that thing.
But the leader of this mission is Tino,
so let's follow her orders.
What?!
But compared to you, I'm complete garbage.
This is also experience.
If it comes down to it,
I'll be there to help.
I'm begging you, Tino!
I mean, taking point is
scary and such a drag!
Understood.
I agree that we need to get out
of here as quickly as possible.
Yes, yes.
With you leading the way, of course.
Yes, sir!
My pain has subsided,
so now I can run properly.
R-Right.
But we also have the people we rescued.
Let's not forget about them.
Oh.
Please forgive me, Master.
Yes, yes.
Of course, I'm the one who
can't keep up whatsoever.
Once we're through here,
we'll almost be at the exit, Master.
I apologize for all of this.
Should that thing appear again,
you can use me as a human shield.
I have no intention of abandoning you.
I will buy you a little time.
So please, at least get
my companions to safety. Please.
As long as we've got Master, we're fine.
All of us will return home alive.
I am in your debt.
Oh, not at all.
Her confidence in me is insane.
If it were just Tino,
I could pick her up and escape...
but doing that for everyone
here is just not happening.
It's my job to be the human shield.
Rudolph took this mission for my sake.
Don't say that, Helian.
You can hash all that out
when this is done.
Once we're safely back in the capital.
Right?
Yes, forgive me.
I knew it.
Master is a god.
Are they getting closer?
This really isn't my day.
I've got five Safety Rings left.
Which means the sixth
time, I really will die.
I've got no other relics I can use.
The Shooting Ring won't even stop them.
And Sitri's Slime is missing.
Plus, I dropped the sword relic I
had tied to my waist somewhere.
Wait...
Could this really be the end?
Stay put over there, you guys!
What is this?
Master.
Something tremendous is coming this way.
It's that thing, for sure!
Master?
Stand back. This is dangerous.
If I use the Night Hiker and
become a human missile,
I'll die once, but I can at
least get a surprise attack in.
I'm so far gone that I'm calm again.
What is that?
I don't know!
It's coming!
What the hell is that thing?
It's dangerous, for sure!
There's no way we can win
against something like that.
A second one!
Preposterous.
Impossible!
Master...
Save us, Master.
This is the end.
I'm so sorry.
I'll try my hardest and do anything!
Just save us!
What are you doing here?
That's...
Liz, ain't it?!
What was that?
What just happened?
I'm just asking to make sure.
When did she...
Are those new members for us?
No.
Also, want to take off that mask?
What a relief.
I figured they weren't, but...
Oh, you dropped this.
This relic is yours, right?
Thanks.
You're welcome!
Is she... human?!
It can't be...
What?
Are you saying you don't know who I am?
Even though Krai's here, too?
Are you even hunters?
Or unregistered?
Are you trying to tell me that
there are people in the capital
who don't know about the Grieving Souls?
I'm really sorry, Krai.
No, it's okay.
I'm really sad, you know?
I actually ran home.
But then I heard you had
gone to a treasure vault.
It makes me sad.
So very, very sad.
And so ashamed!
You know, I actually had faith.
I was sure this had to
be some kind of mistake.
That surely, you're just the worrying type.
Well, I...
But I can't believe...
that my very own apprentice...
can't even handle cleaning up a bunch of trash.
Umm, what do yo—
Gilbert!
You go die!
Can you not see that I'm in
the middle of an apology?!
Potions!
Throw everything you have on him!
Gilbert, are you still alive?
Say, Ti.
Am I just incompetent?
Or did you not get enough training?
Do you lack talent?
Were you slacking?
Or do you lack ambition?
Well? Well?
Hey, answer me!
Answer me, you piece of shit!
You worthless pile of trash!
I don't remember raising you like this!
Everyone will hate me because of you!
If you don't have the drive, just die!
Go die in a ditch before you can
cause trouble for Krai again!
Bite off your tongue and die!
I'm sorry I'm so weak and horrible!
Please forgive me.
Please forgive me!
I'm not the one you should be apologizing to!
Liz, Tino did a really great job today.
She defeated phantoms and
managed the mission as well.
She did really well.
She did?
Really?
Yes, yes!
And you've also gotten
so good at holding back.
I'm proud of you.
Oh, you noticed?
Isn't it amazing?!
You kept insisting,
so I learned how to stop right before...
R-Right.
Stop right before, eh?
I don't know how much you actually stopped,
Wake up!
but you're doing great.
I'm so sorry I caused all
these problems, Master.
You're fine.
Ti does have talent.
All that's lacking is ambition,
effort, and willingness to die.
Yes, yes. You're absolutely right.
What?
That's...!
I am so pissed that we're being
underestimated because of you, Ti.
This is so stupid!
Are you kidding me?!
You think you can hit me
with a measly gun?
I have long surpassed weapons you dragged
up from physical civilizations!
Ti!
Yes, ma'am!
Don't tell me you were actually afraid of
this pathetically slow, wet noodle of a weapon?!
Are you trying to embarrass
me with your incompetence?!
With phantoms like these...
you kill them in their armor!
Kill them from above!
Blow up their heads!
Kill however you like!
It's the most fun thing ever!
With swords, you grab them,
divert them,
or evade them.
Do whatever you want.
Just tell me what you're
having trouble with here!
You know, smash them!
They can't hit you if you kill them first!
They can't dodge if you hit them!
Just do it right!
Put your life on the line!
Got that?
You got it, right, you idiot?!
You'd better start living faster,
cuz you don't have time, Ti!
You gotta work 100 times harder than me!
The gap between us is only
widening, you slowpoke!
You sluggish moron!
Now she's crying.
I feel so bad.
And I was feeling good before!
Goddamn it!
A phantom on par with
Thousand Swords... was it?
Thousand Swords and Liz
kept going up against each other
and mutually improved.
That's how the Grievers became strong.
Me excluded, that is.
Liz, have you calmed down now?
A little, I guess.
Liz Smart.
She is faster than anyone
and anything in this world.
Her godly speed won't even
leave a shadow.
That's why her second name
is "Stifled Shadow."
"Stifled Shadow"
Liz Smart
Hunter Level 6
I'm back, Krai!
Welcome back, Liz.
Thousand Tricks can have
the Purgatorial Sword.
Are you sure?
Isn't it important to you?
I'm starting all over again with my old party.
Make sure you apologize properly.
I will.
You all helped me so much.
Please tell Thousand Tricks I said thanks.
Will do.
Sooner or later, I'm going to be catching
bullets like Stifled Shadow!
Impossible.
I don't know...
Yeah, nope.
Shut up!
If you're trying to get as good as her,
just a word of warning.
- 6 years ago -
The Grievers' masks are custom-made...
I messed up the order.
With these, blinding attacks
won't have an effect on us!
Yeah, our faces are completely protected!
If we can wear these and move as before,
won't we get even stronger?!
That's our Krai!
Yup.
I forgot to make eye holes...
It's not here...
Yeah, it's nowhere to be found.
There's nothing I can do.
I'll just forget about it.
That's what I'll do. Yup.
By: Liz & Ti
Date, date, happy-happy date,
going out with Krai!
Today, I'm feeling good all day!
Uh, so...
Um... Ma'am...
Ti, you go train!
Yes, ma'am!
Next time, on Let This Grieving Soul...
...Retire.
Episode 05
I Want to Leave Everything to Ark
Louder!
Sorry!
"I Want to Leave Everything to Ark."